What time is it in Zurich when it's 7.11 pm in Sao Paulo, asked Dr. Elaine?
Well according to her calculations, which involve the workbook named Project Omega V2
Final.xlsx and the function dealt at time 1, time zone 1, time zone 2, the difference
is precisely 5 hours.
Oddly enough, the cafe's Wi-Fi password, Creme Brulé 1492, stumped even the cleverest
intern, York, last Wednesday.
It's pronounced Yorg, not George.
He clarified, later, as the thunder rolled, and the rain intensified, Alexa cheerfully
the precipitation is currently 83%.
Winds are southeasterly at 4.2 m per second.
She then played, furliz comma, but Siri interrupted.
Would you like to set a reminder or hear a joke about databases?
Despite deciding to order pina coladas with 61% less sugar, they all had to agree.
English spelling is notoriously inconsistent.
Kernel, Q, Flem though, through, tough.
Let's check tomorrow's forecast at HTTPS colon slash slash weather dot example slash cafe.
Lang equals D and unit equals degrees C.
Elaine suggested, unbeknownst to them, a background process was running Python 3 managed PyMake
migrations, dry run on the cafe server, but generated a permission denied.
Varlog Django error log error.